Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X: Audio-Visual Material, 1957-2009
  - Subseries X:A: Audio Cassettes, 1968-2009
    - WOMR: Talking Together - Howard Zinn on Presidents, the Presidency and the Electorate, Feb 21, 1992; cuid17184 (Box 87, Cassette 81)
    - Sender Garlin: Lecture on Jack London - "Romantic Revolutionary", Apr 14, 1992; cuid17185 (Box 87, Cassette 82)
      Duration: 82 Minutes
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 1 "Columbus, the Indians and Human Progress", 1992; cuid17186 (Box 88, Cassette 83)
      Preservation Note: Commercial tape - not transferred
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 2 "Drawing the Color Line", Chapter 4, "Tyranny is Tyranny", 1992; cuid17187 (Box 88, Cassette 84)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 3 "Persons of Mean and Vile Condition", 1992; cuid17188 (Box 88, Cassette 85)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 5 "A Kind Revolution", 1992; cuid17189 (Box 88, Cassette 86)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 6 "The Intimately Oppressed", 1992; cuid17190 (Box 88, Cassette 87)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 7 "As Long as Grass Grows or Water Runs", 1992; cuid17191 (Box 88, Cassette 88)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 8 "We Take Nothing By Conquest, Thank God", 1992; cuid17192 (Box 88, Cassette 89)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 9 "Slavery Without Submission, Emancipation Without Freedom", 1992; cuid17193 (Box 88, Cassette 90)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 9 continued, Chapter 10 "The Other Civil War", 1992; cuid17194 (Box 88, Cassette 91)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 10 continued, 1992; cuid17195 (Box 88, Cassette 92)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 11 "Robber Barons and Rebels", 1992; cuid17196 (Box 88, Cassette 93)
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States, Read by Geri Librandi - Chapter 11 continued, 1992; cuid17197 (Box 88, Cassette 94)
    - Howard Zinn: "Columbus Legacy: 1492-1992" (California Polytechnic, CA), cuid17198 (Box 87, Cassette 95)
      Duration: 92 Minutes
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, "Emma Goldman: Dangerous Woman" (Radcliffe College, Cambridge, MA), Feb 24, 1993; cuid17199 (Box 87, Cassette 96)
      Duration: 64 Minutes
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, "Emma Goldman: Dangerous Woman" (Radcliffe College, Cambridge, MA), Feb 24, 1993; cuid17200 (Box 87, Cassette 96 dup)
      Preservation Note: Dupe. Did Not digitize
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The New Patriotism; War, Peace and Me" (Newbury College, Brookline, MA), Apr 20, 1993; cuid17201 (Box 87, Cassette 97)
    - Howard Zinn: "Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity" (Harvey Goldberg Lecture Series, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI) Tape 1, [Sep 1993]; cuid17202 (Box 87, Cassette 98)
      Duration: 65 min.
    - Howard Zinn: "Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity" (Harvey Goldberg Lecture Series, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI) Tape 2, [Sep 1993]; cuid17203 (Box 87, Cassette 99)
      Duration: 29 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Use and Abuse of History" (University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH), Mar 9, 1994; cuid17204 (Box 87, Cassette 100)
      Duration: 77 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Use and Abuse of History" (University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH), Mar 9, 1994; cuid17205 (Box 87, Cassette 100 dup)
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Clinton Administration: Its Historical Perspective" (University of Maine, Farmington, ME), Mar 29, 1994; cuid17206 (Box 87, Cassette 101)
      Duration: 92 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Talking Together Lecture: Howard Zinn, "Can History Prepare Us for the Twenty-First Century?" (Wellfleet Public Library, Wellfleet, MA), Aug 11, 1994; cuid17207 (Box 87, Cassette 102)
      Duration: 90 min.
    - Talking Together: Howard Zinn - "Can History Prepare Us for the Twenty-First Century?" (Wellfleet Public Library, Wellfleet, MA), Aug 11, 1994; cuid17208 (Box 87, Cassette 103)
      Duration: 94 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn - "The Use and Abuse of History" (St Michael's College, Winooski, VT), Oct 4, 1994; cuid17209 (Box 87, Cassette 104)
      Duration: 93 min.
    - WPR: Ideas Network - Howard Zinn Interviewed by Jean Feraca on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (Madison, WI), Nov 29, 1994; cuid17210 (Box 87, Cassette 105)
      Duration: 53 min.
    - Howard Zinn: Myth and Reality in the Teaching of American History (Chautauqua Institution, Chautauqua, NY), 1994; cuid17211 (Box 87, Cassette 106)
      Duration: 76 min.
    - Second Opinion / The Progressive: Howard Zinn, Interviewed by Matthew Rothschild on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (also includes interview with Marita Golden), Feb 10, 1995/Feb 17, 1995; cuid17212 (Box 87, Cassette 107)
      Duration: 80 min.
    - WOMR: Talking Together - Howard Zinn Interviewed by Matthew Rothschild on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train (Broadcast May 4, 1995), Feb 10, 1995; cuid17213 (Box 87, Cassette 108)
      Duration: 62 min.
    - Radio Free Maine: Howard Zinn, You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train - Education and Activism, Feb 13, 1995; cuid17214 (Box 87, Cassette 109)
    - David Barsamian: "Corporate Power, Profits Before People" (Santa Cruz, CA), Oct 13, 1995; cuid17215 (Box 87, Cassette 110)
      Duration: 74 min.
    - Howard Zinn: A People's History of the United States (Portland, OR), Nov 20, 1995; cuid17216 (Box 87, Cassette 111)
      Duration: 60 min.
    - City Arts of San Francisco: Alice Walker and Howard Zinn in Discussion on Writing and Activism, Hosted by Maya Angelou (San Francisco, CA), [1995]; cuid17217 (Box 87, Cassette 112)
      Duration: 59 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - Women's Foundation of California / City Arts: Alice Walker in Discussion with Howard Zinn, Jan 17, 1996; cuid17218 (Box 87, Cassette 113)
    - WBAI: Howard Zinn - Lecture on History, Education and Objectivity (Fullerton College, Fullerton, CA) / Chris Whent Radio Show, Oct 12, 1996/Jun 6, 1992; cuid17219 (Box 87, Cassette 114)
      Duration: 127 Minutes
      Content is several radio episodes from WBAI - Only the first 11 1/2 minutes on side 2 is Zinn related
    - Alice Walker: My Life as My Self, 1996; cuid17220 (Box 87, Cassette 115)
    - KPFA: Anything We Love Can Be Saved - Mothers' Day Eve with Alice Walker (King Middle School, Berkeley, CA), May 10, 1997; cuid17221 (Box 87, Cassette 116)
      Duration: 86 Mintues
    - WORT: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn Interviewed by James Carrott on You Can't Be Neutral on a Moving Train, Jul 15, 1997; cuid17222 (Box 87, Cassette 117)
    - KPFA: Mario Savio Memorial Lecture - Howard Zinn "The Possibility of Hope: Our Legacy from the Sixties," University of California, Berkeley, CA, Nov 13, 1997; cuid17223 (Box 87, Cassette 118)
      Duration: 89 Minutes
    - WORT: A Public Affair - Howard Zinn (Interview on the Uses of History), Nov 18, 1997; cuid17224 (Box 87, Cassette 119)
      Duration: 64 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2: 10 1/2 minute gap in content (00:04:06;xx - 00:14:48;xx)
    - Howard Zinn: Lecture on the Uses of History (Wisconsin Historical Society, Madison, WI), Nov 18, 1997; cuid17225 (Box 87, Cassette 120)
    - Howard Zinn: Lecture on History, Politics and Objectivity (Portland, OR), Jan 22, 1998; cuid17226 (Box 87, Cassette 121)
    - Howard Zinn: One Hundred Years of U.S. Imperialism (Old Cambridge Baptist Church, Cambridge, MA), Jun 30, 1998; cuid17227 (Box 87, Cassette 122)
    - Alternative Radio: Eqbal Ahmad - "Terrorism: Theirs and Ours" (Boulder, CO), Oct 12, 1998; cuid17228 (Box 87, Cassette 123)
    - Alternative Radio: Eqbal Ahmad - Boulder Interviews (Boulder, CO), Oct 12, 1998-Oct 13, 1998; cuid17229 (Box 87, Cassette 124)
    - People's Tribune Radio: Howard Zinn, A Working Class Citizen's Economic Bill of Rights, Also Includes Nelson Peery, Oct 1998; cuid17230 (Box 88, Cassette 125)
    - Howard Zinn: Bringing Democracy Alive (University of Colorado, Denver, CO) Tape 1, 1998; cuid17231 (Box 88, Cassette 126)
      Duration: 63 Minutes
    - Howard Zinn: Bringing Democracy Alive (University of Colorado, Denver, CO) Tape 2, 1998; cuid17232 (Box 88, Cassette 127)
      Duration: 34 Minutes
    - WNYC: New York and Company - Howard Zinn (Interview), Jan 15, 1999; cuid17233 (Box 88, Cassette 128)
      Duration: 39 Minutes
    - WUSB: Critique - Howard Zinn (Interview, Stony Brook, NY), [Feb 1, 1999]; cuid17234 (Box 88, Cassette 129)
      Duration: 95 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2: Final 2/3 is non-Zinn related
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - War and Democracy (Chestnut Hill, MA), Nov 11, 1999; cuid17235 (Box 88, Cassette 130)
      Duration: 59 Minutes
    - Common Courage Press: "Zinn at the Heart of History: An Interview with Howard Zinn by Greg Bates on Objectivity and Optimism", 1999; cuid17236 (Box 88, Cassette 131)
      Duration: 51 Minutes
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn (Interview, Stony Brook, NY), Jan 29, 2000; cuid17237 (Box 88, Cassette 132)
      Duration: 36 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - WNYC: New York and Company - Interviews on Howard Zinn on History and Howard Zinn on War, [2000]; cuid17238 (Box 88, Cassette 133)
      Duration: 46 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - Alternative Radio: Arundhati Roy - "A Writer's Place in Politics" (Amherst, MA), Feb 15, 2001; cuid17239 (Box 88, Cassette 134)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - "Artists in a Time of War" (Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, MA), Oct 10, 2001; cuid17240 (Box 88, Cassette 135)
    - Alternative Radio: Howard Zinn - "Artists in a Time of War" (Massachusetts College of Art, Boston, MA), Oct 10, 2001; cuid17241 (Box 88, Cassette 135 dup)
      Preservation Note: Duplicate - did not digitize
    - WMBR: Anti-War Rally in Boston / Nov 2001 News (Democracy Rising Tour and Day of Mourning), Oct 12, 2001/Nov 2001; cuid17242 (Box 88, Cassette 136)
      Duration: 61 Minutes
    - WAMU: Howard Zinn Interviewed by Diane Rehm on Terrorism and War, the Anti-War Movement and Alternatives to War (American University, Washington, DC), Jul 11, 2002; cuid17243 (Box 88, Cassette 137)
    - Howard Zinn: Interview on "A Break-in for Peace," Article on the Camden 28 Published in The Progressive (July 2002), Jul 22, 2002; cuid17244 (Box 88, Cassette 138)
      Duration: 47 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 1: Final third is non-Zinn related; Side 2 is blank
    - WBUR / NPR: The Connection - "Where's the Opposition?: The Left's Position on the Iraq War" (includes Peter Lems, Leo Ribuffo and Congresswoman Barbara Lee), Sep 17, 2002; cuid17245 (Box 88, Cassette 139)
      Duration: 62 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview (Stony Brook, NY), May 19, 2003; cuid17246 (Box 88, Cassette 140)
      Duration: 47 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview (Stony Brook, NY), Mar 28, 2005; cuid17247 (Box 88, Cassette 141)
      Duration: 48 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - WAMU: Howard Zinn Interviewed by Diane Rehm on Voices of a People's History of the United States (American University, Washington, DC), May 2, 2005; cuid17248 (Box 88, Cassette 142)
      Duration: 53 Minutes
    - WUSB: Howard Zinn - Interview on A Power Governments Cannot Suppress (Stony Brook, NY), Jan 20, 2007; cuid17249 (Box 88, Cassette 143)
    - KVSC Newswatch: Howard Zinn Interview on Voices of a People's History of the United States, Dec 13, 2009; cuid17250 (Box 88, Cassette 144)
      Duration: 21 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Race and Law, Oct 12; cuid17251 (Box 88, Cassette 145)
      Tape was slated to be digitized in 2015 but could not be due to binder hydrolysis. It was kept for incubation and baking, but transfer was unsuccessful as of 2017.
    - Dial a Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (also includes music and other interviews), undated; cuid17252 (Box 88, Cassette 146)
    - Diane Valcourt's Audio Journal for Howard Zinn (PO 394), undated; cuid17253 (Box 88, Cassette 147)
      Duration: 17 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 2 is blank
    - Documentary on Emma Goldman, undated; cuid17254 (Box 88, Cassette 148)
    - Emma: A Play in Two Acts about Emma Goldman, American Anarchist by Howard Zinn: Performance in French, undated; cuid17255 (Box 88, Cassette 149)
      Duration: 56 Minutes
    - Eqbal Ahmed on Progressive Movements in Pakistan Tape 4, undated; cuid17256 (Box 88, Cassette 150)
    - "Freedom and Democracy": Spoken Word by Howard Zinn and Music by Steve Lutke and James Voris, undated; cuid17257 (Box 89, Cassette 151)
      Duration: 10 Minutes
    - "Freedom and Democracy": Spoken Word by Howard Zinn and Music by Steve Lutke and James Voris, undated; cuid17258 (Box 89, Cassette 151 dup)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Bacon's Rebellion (poor audio quality), undated; cuid17259 (Box 89, Cassette 152)
      Duration: 45 Minutes, Preservation Note: As noted: poor audio quality; Side 2 is blank
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Central America and Just and Unjust Wars, undated; cuid17260 (Box 89, Cassette 153)
      Duration: 119 Minutes
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Civil Disobedience Versus Voting (Tactics) / Bill Baird: Lecture to Howard Zinn's Class / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Daniel Berrigan, undated; cuid17261 (Box 89, Cassette 154)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Political Theory and Ideology, undated; cuid17262 (Box 89, Cassette 155)
      Duration: 65 Minutes
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on the State and the Individual / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Human Nature, undated; cuid17263 (Box 89, Cassette 156)
    - Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Tactics (Tape 1) / Howard Zinn: Class Lecture on Women's Suffrage, undated; cuid17264 (Box 89, Cassette 157)
      Duration: 113 Minutes
    - Howard Zinn: Interview with David Barsamian, undated; cuid17265 (Box 89, Cassette 158)
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel in Discussion: Introduced by Alice Walker (Berkeley, CA), undated; cuid17266 (Box 89, Cassette 159)
      Duration: 95 Minutes, Preservation Note: Side 1: @ 00:07:17;xx - very brief (less than second) piece content not captured due to tape malfunction.
    - Howard Zinn and Studs Terkel in Discussion: Introduced by Alice Walker (edited, Berkeley, CA), undated; cuid17267 (Box 89, Cassette 160)
      This is an edited version of cuid17266
    - Howard Zinn: Unidentified [Microcassette], undated; cuid17268 (Box 87, Cassette 161)
      Duration: 61 Minutes, Preservation Note: This is a microcassette - not a an 1/8" audiocassette; Side 1: @00:17:13;xx Content changes from lecture to conversation and the speed changes from 24cm to 12cm; Side 2: entire content has a 24cm speed.
    - Marx in Soho by Howard Zinn (performed by Hal Fuller, directed by [Don Devecio]), undated; cuid17269 (Box 89, Cassette 162)
    - Marx in Soho by Howard Zinn: Performance in Italian, undated; cuid17270 (Box 89, Cassette 163)
      Duration: 7 Minutes
      Side 2 is blank
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (edited), undated; cuid17271 (Box 89, Cassette 164)
    - New Hampshire Public Radio: Howard Zinn - Interview (edited), undated; cuid17272 (Box 89, Cassette 164 dup)
  - Subseries X:B: Audio Compact Disks, 1968-2009
    - Rev. Daniel Berrigan and Howard Zinn: Hanoi: Release of US Airmen (transfer from tape), 1968; cuid17273 (Box 75, Cd 165)
    - Howard Zinn at Maryville College, Fall 1969; cuid17274 (Box 75, Cd 166)
    - Howard Zinn's Last Class at Boston University, 1988; cuid17275 (Box 75, Cd 167)
    - Howard Zinn: "A People's History of the United States, A Lecture at Reed College" (AK Press Studio), 1998; cuid17276 (Box 75, Cd 168)
    - Howard Zinn: "A People's History of the United States, A Lecture at Reed College" (AK Press Studio), 1998; cuid17277 (Box 75, Cd 168 dup)
    - Noam Chomsky, Jimmy Tingle, Howard Zinn: "An Evening of Conversation, Confrontation and Comedy, A Benefit for Wellfleet Harbor Actors Theater", Aug 3, 2001; cuid17278 (Box 75, Cd 169)
    - Howard Zinn: "Heroes and Martyrs-Emma Goldman, Sacco and Vanzetti, and the Revolutionary Struggle" (AK Press Studio), 2001; cuid17279 (Box 75, Cd 170)
    - Howard Zinn: "Stories Hollywood Never Tells Us" (AK Press Studio), 2001; cuid17280 (Box 75, Cd 171)
    - Noam Chomsky and Howard Zinn (Photo CD), 2001-2002; cuid17281 (Box 75, Cd 172)
    - Howard Zinn: "Terrorism and War", Jun 17, 2002; cuid17282 (Box 75, Cd 173)
    - Howard Zinn: "Artists in a Time of War" (AK Press Audio), 2002; cuid17283 (Box 75, Cd 174)
    - Howard Zinn: "Civics Education: Patriotism of Skepticism" NPR's Justice Talking (The Annenberg Public Policy Center, University of Pennsylvania), 2002; cuid17284 (Box 75, Cd 175)
    - " A People's History of the United States, Highlights from the Twentieth Century" Read by Howard Zinn and Matt Damon (Harper Collins Publishers, Inc.) 4 CD set, 2002; cuid17285 (Box 75, Cd 177)
    - Howard Zinn (Photo CD), 2002-2008; cuid17286 (Box 75, Cd 178)
    - Howard Zinn: "USA and the War: Historic Perspective" (The Palestinian Radio Show at CKUT, 90.3 FM, Montreal, Quebec), Jan 20, 2003; cuid17287 (Box 75, Cd 179)
    - Howard Zinn Tribute - Voices from A People's History (92nd Street Y, New York City), Feb 23, 2003; cuid17288 (Box 75, Cd 180)
    - Howard Zinn: "History and War on Iraq" (Global Voices for Justice), Nov 3, 2003; cuid17289 (Box 75, Cd 181)
    - Howard Zinn: "Free and Fair" (KAOS, 89.2 FM, Olympia, WA), Dec 5, 2003; cuid17290 (Box 75, Cd 182)
    - Howard Zinn: "A Personal History" (Commonwealth Journal, Produced by WUMB Radio, University of Massachusetts, Boston), 2003; cuid17291 (Box 75, Cd 183)
    - Howard Zinn: "Why Civil Disobedience Matters" (KUCI, 88.9 FM, Irvine CA, Program "Justice or Just Us"), [2003]; cuid17292 (Box 75, Cd 184)
    - Howard Zinn: "Artists in Times of War" (Cambridge Forum Radio), Jan 21, 2004; cuid17293 (Box 75, Cd 185)
    - Howard Zinn and Noam Chomsky: "Is There Hope in this Desperate Time?" (Radio Free Maine), Sep 27, 2004; cuid17294 (Box 75, Cd 186)
    - "The Outsider in American Politics" from the Marc Steiner Show "America's Future: 2004" (88.1 WYPR, Baltimore MD), Oct 7, 2004; cuid17295 (Box 75, Cd 187)
    - Howard Zinn et al: "Voices from a People's History" (New York, NY, Alternative Radio) Part 1, Oct 22, 2004; cuid17296 (Box 75, Cd 188)
    - Howard Zinn et al: "Voices from a People's History" (New York, NY, Alternative Radio) Part 2, Oct 22, 2004; cuid17297 (Box 75, Cd 189)
    - "Voices of a People's History": New York Society of Ethical Culture (2 CD set), Oct 22, 2004; cuid17298 (Box 75, Cd 190)
    - Howard Zinn: "Class and War in U.S. Society, A Critique" (Maxve Societal Press), Oct 27, 2004; cuid17299 (Box 75, Cd 191)
    - Howard Zinn: "Empire, Resistance and the War in Iraq" (Keynote Speech, Historians Against the War Conference, Austin, TX) Disk 1, Feb 17, 2006; cuid17300 (Box 75, Cd 192)
    - Howard Zinn and Anthony Arnove: "Voices of a People's History of the United States" (Lannan Readings and Conversations) Disk 2 of 2, Apr 26, 2006; cuid17301 (Box 75, Cd 193)
    - Howard Zinn: "The Inner Life of Democracy" (Cambridge Forum Radio), Oct 25, 2006; cuid17302 (Box 75, Cd 194)
    - Howard Zinn: "Overcoming Obstacles" (Boulder, CO, Alternative Radio), Nov 30, 2006; cuid17303 (Box 75, Cd 195)
    - Howard Zinn: "Overcoming Obstacles" (Boulder, CO Alternative Radio), Nov 30, 2006; cuid17304 (Box 75, Cd 195 dup)
    - "Readings from Voices of a People's History of the United States," (Seven Stories Press), 2006; cuid17305 (Box 75, Cd 196)
    - Performance of Marx in Soho with Robert Weick, Feb 15, 2007; cuid17306 (Box 75, Cd 197)
    - Howard Zinn: Question and Answer Session after Performance of Marx in Soho, Feb 15, 2007; cuid17307 (Box 75, Cd 198)
    - "Rebel Voices" Performances (stage adaptation of Voices of A People's History of the United States), Dec 11, 2007, Dec 16, 2007; cuid17308 (Box 75, Cd 199)
    - Howard Zinn: "Reflections on War" (Commonwealth Journal, Prodcued by WUMB Radio, University of Massachusetts, Boston), 2007; cuid17309 (Box 75, Cd 200)
    - Howard Zinn Readings (Photo CD), Jan 8, 2008; cuid17310 (Box 75, Cd 201)
    - "America, Empire of Liberty": Panel Discussion (Howard Zinn participating) on BBC Radio, Sep 2008; cuid17311 (Box 75, Cd 202)
    - "Sacco and Vanzetti 08" (companion piece to news report from Boston about Anarchists marking the 81st Anniversary of the execution of Sacco and Vanzetti), 2008; cuid17312 (Box 75, Cd 203)
    - "Living with the Consequences, The Legacy of the U.S. Policy in Nicaragua" (Photos of Page Proofs for Book) Part 1, [2008]; cuid17313 (Box 75, Cd 204)
    - "Living with the Consequences, The Legacy of the U.S. Policy in Nicaragua" (Photos of Page Proofs for Book) Part 2, [2008]; cuid17314 (Box 75, Cd 205)
    - "Americans Who Tell the Truth (and other recent Social Justice reports produced by Chuck U. Rosina)", Jan 2009-Apr 2009; cuid17315 (Box 75, Cd 206)
    - Marx a Roma Radio Performance (Also second disk that includes 2 bitmap images and an MP3 file), Jun 2009; cuid17316 (Box 75, Cd 207)
    - Marx in Soho Music Compilation, undated; cuid17317 (Box 75, Cd 208)
    - Emma Act 2 Scenes 13-15, undated; cuid17318 (Box 75, Cd 209)
    - Rossi Interview with Zinn (in Italian), undated; cuid17319 (Box 75, Cd 210)
  - Subseries X:C: Audio Reel-to-Reel, 1957-1975
    - Howard Zinn: Spanish-American War, (Denver CO, 5 Inch), Jul 16, 1957; cuid17320 (Box 76, Reel 211)
      Duration: 15 Minutes
    - Panel Discussion with Spelman College's First Exchange Students: Includes Sharon Passow, Mary Millen, Martha Thiessen, Mary Anne Peterson, Jackee Walken, May 1960; cuid17321 (Box 76, Reel 212)
      Duration: 87 Minutes
    - Sit-In Showdown: Includes Music, Dance Performance and Comedy Tape 1, May 17, 1960; cuid17322 (Box 76, Reel 213)
      Duration: 115 Minutes
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): "China: Past and Present", "East and West", Lecture on Confucianism, Discussion of Menicus and Hsun-tze, Sep 26, 1961; cuid17323 (Box 76, Reel 214)
      Duration: 185 Minutes
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Session on the Chinese Language, Sep 27, 1961; cuid17324 (Box 76, Reel 215)
      Duration: 136 Minutes
    - Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): "China: Past and Present," "Legalism and Confucianism" (also includes Hocking seminar on Confucianism), Sep 30, 1961; cuid17325 (Box 76, Reel 216)
    - Meet the Press: Ambassador Tsiang on Nationalist China / Non-Western Program 1961-1962 (Atlanta University Center): Faculty Seminar - Chinese History, Oct 8, 1961/Oct 10, 1961; cuid17326 (Box 76, Reel 217)
      Duration: 144 Minutes
    - Martin Luther King Jr. at Town Hall Meeting on Non-Violence (Atlanta University, GA) / Radio Broadcast: "The South: 1961" (Baptist Revival), Oct 12, 1961/Nov 12, 1961; cuid17327 (Box 86, Box 76, Reel 218)
      Access Copies
      An access copy of this recording (3 CDs) is available in box 86 of this collection.
      Duration: 104 Minutes